John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, Corporate Structure, RG 1 FA1793
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Board of Trustees, 1950-2019; 1; 33.99 Cubic Feet 87 letter document boxes and 5 half-letter boxes
  - Meetings, 1950-2019; 6; 11.01 Cubic Feet 28 letter document boxes, 2 half-letter box
    - Board Books, 1986-2009; 2
      - Board Book, 1989 March (Box 4, Folder 1)
        Writeups of approved grants for: Cathedral School Fund, Three Rivers Literacy Alliance, Virginia Beach Foundation, Young Horizons, Law Enforcement Foundation, Goodwill Industries of Michiana, Florida Keys Land Trust, Limberlost Girl Scout Council, Presbyterian Settlement Work Council, Conservation Corps of Long Beach, Miami Rescue Mission, American Press Institute, Goodwill Industries-Big Bend, Shepherd's Center of Charlotte, Better Way Foundation, YMCA of Tucson, Girl Scout Council of Santa Clara County, Queens College, Native American Press Association, Michigan Opera Theatre, Virginia Air and Space Center and the Hampton Roads History Center, Northwest Indiana Symphony Society, Columbus Philharmonic Guild, East Michigan Environmental Action Council, Dyslexia Research Institute, Camp Fowler, Info Line Incorporated, Boys Village, American Council for the Arts, Philharmonic Orchestra of Florida, Keep Akron Beautiful, Akron Regional Development Board Educational Fund, The Buckeye Chapter John S. Knight Memorial Journalism Fund Inc., Manatee Players, Friends of the North Dakota Museum of Art, Manatee Junior College, National Foundation for Advancement in the Arts, Florida West Coast Music, San Jose Hospital Foundation, City Center Ballet of San Jose, University of Florida-Florida Museum of Natural History, Miami City Ballet, Memorial Hospital of Long Beach, Asolo Performing Arts Center, Ocean Inc., Greater Akron Musical Association, Northern Indiana Art Association, Musical Arts Association, Athletes Learning Educational Resources Training, Rensselaerville Institute, Friends of the Waccamaw Library, Volunteers of America of Kentucky, Dance Critics Association, Seamens Church Institute of New York and New Jersey, American Music Theater Festival, Junior League of Miami, McAuley Education Center, Christian Community Service Agency, North Carolina Arts Council, Akron 70001 Retail Skills Training Center, Wm. H. Spencer Golden Owlettes, Easter Seal Society of Rhode Island, International Press Institute. Writeups for negative responses to proposals are also included.
      - Board Book, 1989 June (Box 4, Folder 2)
        Writeups of approved grants for: Midsummer Macon, Family Focus, Institute of Logopedics, Pennsylvania Opera Theater, First Amendment Congress, Pasadena Educational Foundation, Cranbrook Educational Community, Battered Womens Shelter, Northeastern Educational Television of Ohio, Friends of Independence National Historic Park, Junior Achievement, Washington Journalism Center, Pennsylvania Humanities Council, Manatee County Girls Club, Schiele Museum of Natural History and Planetarium, Institute for Journalism Education, Ohio University Fund, United Way of the St. Paul Area, Emergency Family Assistance Association, Association for Retarded Citizens of Allen County, Settlement Music School of Philadelphia, School of Journalism Foundation of North Carolina, Arlington Church of God, Common Ground, Goodwill Industries of South Florida, Long Beach Ballet, College Assistance Program of Dade County, Tallahassee YMCA, Allen County Fairgrounds, Philadelphia Orchestra Association, Philadelphia Urban Coalition Foundation, People's Emergency Center, Bill Wilson Marriage and Family Counseling Center, Council on Aging of the Midlands, Boy Scouts of America, Saint Paul-Ramsey United Arts Council, Furnace Street Mission, United Citizens Organization of East Chicago, Fund for the Advancement of Science and Mathematics Education in North Carolina, Consortium for the Advancement of Private Higher Education, Hanna Perkins School, Painted Bride Art Center, University of Akron Foundation. Writeups for negative responses to proposals are also included.
      - Board Book, 1989 September (Box 4, Folder 3)
        Writeups of approved grants for: Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press, Wichita State University Endowment Association, St. Alban's Day Nursery, Broward Public Library Foundation, James E. Scott Community Association Inc., Boy Scouts of America Central Georgia Council, Faith Counseling Center, Lexington Hearing and Speech Center, Interval Brotherhood Homes Corporation, Please Touch Museum, YWCA Duluth, Grand Forks Public Schools, San Jose Museum of Art Association, Clark County Association for Handicapped Citizens, Harvard Crimson Trust II, Pennsylvania Ballet Association, San Jose Repertory Company, Ransom Everglades School, Gulf Coast Opera Theatre, Reading is Fundamental, Jobs for Progress, Attic Theatre, Boy Scouts of America Bluegrass Council, Kent State University Foundation, Fort Wayne Civic Theatre, Asbury College, Boca Raton Symphonic Pops Inc., Marygrove College, Children's Concert Society of Akron, Movement Theatre International Inc, Youth Service Inc., Zoological Society of Florida, Foundation for Hope, University of Iowa, Saint Paul Foundation, Campaign Finance Research Institute, Kentucky Bicentennial Commission, Boy Scouts of America Long Beach Area Council, Salvation Army Milledgeville, Detroit Institute for Children, United Way of Kentucky, People in Faith United Housing Corporation, Stanford University Lucile Salter Packard Children's Hospital, Eton Academy, Oriana House, Dade Public Education Fund, Pathway Society, Boy Scouts of America Santa Clara County Council Incorporated, Long Beach Unified School District, Yellow Springs Institute for Contemporary Studies and the Arts, Joy of Jesus, Duke University Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, Mote Marine Laboratory, Wayne State University, Metropolitan Center for High Technology, American Federation of Arts. Writeups of negative responses to proposals are also included.
      - Board Book, 1989 December (Box 4, Folder 4)
        Writeups of approved grants for: Hindman Settlement School, Florida State University Foundation, NAACP Special Contribution Fund, Union College, Long Beach Symphony Association, Summit County Public Schools, St. Michael's Farm for Boys, Philadelphia Maritime Museum, Memorial Hospital Foundation, Foundation for the Carolinas, United Negro College Fund, Science Museum of Minnesota, Ida Cason Callaway, Opportunities Industrialization Center of America, Manatee County Council for the Arts, Elderly Interest Fund, World Press Institute, Boys Clubs of Broward County, Recording for the Blind Inc. Miami Unit, Community Health Services of Mecklenburg and Union, Frontier Nursing Service Foundation, YMCA Columbus, Salvation Army Eastern Michigan Division, Lincoln Cultural Development Center, American Society of Newspaper Editors Foundation, Big Brothers/Big Sisters of Broward, The Foundation Center, Christian Appalachian Project, Akron Public Schools, Crossroad/Fort Wayne Children's Home, Orchards Children's Services, Opera Guild of Greater Miami, Broward Community College Foundation, Retired Senior Volunteer Program of Montgomery County Pennsylvania, Developmental Disabilities Center, Services for the Aging, Phenix City Russell County Council for Abused and Neglected Children, Literacy Volunteers of America, Goodwill Industries of Akron Ohio, Ordway Music Theatre, South Dade Jewish Community Center, Associated Press Managing Editors Foundation, Children's Home Society of Minnesota, Baldwin County Board of Commissioners, Habitat for Humanity of Charlotte, YMCA of Greater Long Beach, Manatee County Public Library Foundation, Moore Community House Inc., Columbus Museum, Akron Zoological Park, Central Kentucky Radio Eye, Community School of the Arts, Family Service of Long Beach, Mount De Sales Academy, Senior Society Planning Council, Second Harvest Food Bank of Santa Clara and San Mateo Counties, New Children's Shelter Fund, Friends University, Greater Wichita Community Foundation, Macon Independent Schools Association, Macon Substance Abuse Foundation for Education, Oakland Family Services, Miami Coalition, Boulder County Safehouse, Calumet College, SSM Health System-Mercy Hospice of Horry County, Leadership Long Beach, American Council on Education, New World Symphony, Film Society of Miami, North Country Ride, Fort Wayne Medical Society Foundation, H.M. Life Opportunity Services, Charlotte Shakespeare Company, Sanibel-Captiva Conservation Foundation, YWCA in Santa Clara Valley, Pennsylvania State University School of Communications, Junior Achievement of the Upper Midwest, Georgetown College, Center for the Fine Arts Association, Sumter Historic Preservation Society, John Carroll University, National Urban League, Crisis Assistance Ministry, American Red Cross Central South Carolina Chapter, Council on Aging of the Midlands. Writeups for negative responses to proposals are also included.
      - Board Book, 1990 March (Box 4, Folder 5)
        Writeups of approved grants for: Zoological Society of Philadelphia, Committee for the Study of the American Electorate, Philharmonic Orchestra of Florida, Hospice of Palm Beach County, American Press Institute, Community Health Affiliates, Macon Substance Abuse Foundation for Education, Rainbow Community Organization, Miami Dade Community College Foundation, YMCA of Fort Wayne, Philadelphia College of Pharmacy and Science, American Music Theater Festival, Minnesota Program Development, Good Neighbors, Committee to Protect Journalists, Cuyahoga Valley National Recreation Area, Point Breeze Federation, Young Horizons, Fund for Peace, Boy Scouts of America Indian Waters Council, Literacy Volunteers of America, University of Akron Foundation, Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press, Interlochen Center for the Arts, YMCA Grand Forks, Cedars Medical Center Foundation, Northwest Indiana Forum Foundation, Family Counseling Center, Business Volunteers for the Arts, Independent Sector, Down's Syndrome Educational Systems, Brookgreen Gardens, Coastal Community Concert Association, Goodwill Industries of Kentucky, Racial and Ethnic Bias Study Commission, Children's Center of Wayne County, Washington Press Club Foundation, The Clay Studio, Historic Rosedale Foundation, YMCA of Greater Miami, Performing Tree, Eastern Kentucky University Foundation, Lutheran Social Service of Minnesota, San Juan Children's Learning Center, Florida West Coast Music, Planned Parenthood Association of Greater Miami, Hiram College, Museum of Aviation at Robins Air Force Base-Georgia Foundation, Arts Midwest, The Shepherd's House, Akron Rotary Camp for Crippled Children, Opera San Jose, MDC Inc., American Press Institute, Bakehouse Art Complex, Quetico Lifecare Corporation, City of Paramount, Stewart Community Home, Columbus Philharmonic Guild, Columbia Stage Society, Hope Haven, Greater Akron Musical Association, YWCA Pasadena-Foothill Valley, San Francisco State University, YMCA Pasadena, National Drug Council. Writeups for negative responses to proposals are also included.
      - Board Book, 19990 September (Box 5, Folder 1)
        Writeups of approved grants for: Literacy Volunteers of New York City, Russell County Shelter for Battered Women, Fund for Peace, United Cerebral Palsy of Northeastern Minnesota, Akron Art Museum, Emergency Housing Consortium of Santa Clara County, The Balch Institute, Michigan State University, American Leadership Forum Silicon Valley Chapter, Lexington Rape Crisis Center, Foxfire Fund Eastern Kentucky Teachers Network, Foundation for Mental Health Northeastern South Dakota, Actors Contemporary Ensemble, Community Rehabilitation Industries, Zenon Dance Company and Schools, Salvation Army Biloxi, Kentucky Science and Technology Council, Treasure Coast Private Industry Council, Broward County Film Society, Alexander Children's Center, American Refugee Committee, The Beaumont Foundation, The Edison Institute, Laos Inc., Gulf Coast Opera Theatre, Girl Scout Council of Tropical Florida, Rochester Institute of Technology, Point Breeze Performing Arts Center, South Florida Youth Symphony, Philadelphia Neighborhood Enterprise, Family Focus, Children's Concert Society of Akron, Long Bay Symphonic Society, University of Maryland Foundation, Belafonte Tacolcy Center, Southern Scholarship Foundation, Planned Parenthood of Greater Charlotte, Episcopal Outreach of Pawleys Island, American Council for the Arts, Tallahassee Junior Museum, Friends of the Morikami, Curtis Institute of Music, Miami Book Fair International, Detroit Executive Service Corps, Family Services of Summit County, Christian Outreach Appeal, York Technical College Foundation, United States Olympic Committee, Northern Indiana Local Initiatives Support Corporation, Summit County Children Services Board, Tallahassee Housing Foundation, Museum of National Jewish History, God's Pantry-Crisis Food Center, Yale University, Historical Society of Philadelphia, Alpha Library Committee, Broward House, California History Center Foundation, Congaree Girl Scout Area Council, Donors Forum of Ohio, Planned Parenthood League, Twin Cities Habitat for Humanity, Michigan Opera Theatre, Center City Housing Corporation, Milledgeville Baldwin County Allied Arts Inc., Main Line Center of the Arts, Centre County Youth Service Bureau, State College Area YMCA, Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Writeups for negative responses to proposals are also included.
      - Board Book, 1990 December (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
        Writeups of approved grants for: Sexual Assault Program of Northern St. Louis County, Antioch University, NAACP Special Contribution Fund, Summit County Adult Literacy Council, Nonprofit Development Center, The Downtown Center for Children, Public Private Ventures, American Society of Newspaper Editors Foundation, Wayne State University, Rollins College, Dade Marine Institute, Eastfield Ming Quong Foundation, Pace Center for Girls/Manatee, Goodwill Industries of Southern Los Angeles County, Haven Center, United Negro College Fund, National Press Foundation, Forward in the Fifth, Native American Press Association, Music Hall Center for the Performing Arts, Boys Clubs of Long Beach, Public Interest Law Center of Philadelphia, Dr. John T. MacDonald Health Systems, Historic Florida Keys Preservation Board, World Press Institute, St. Marks Center, Bay Mills Community College, Historic Preservation Foundation of North Carolina, United States South Africa Leader Exchange Program, Southern Newspaper Publishers Association Foundation, University of Kentucky College of Business and Economics, Youth News Service Los Angeles Bureau, Western Reserve Girl Scout Council, Focus, Hope, Hezekiah Alexander Foundation, Rose Hill Center, Southwest Community Enrichment Center, O'Connor Hospital, Sedgwick County Zoological Foundation, The Lexington Children's Museum, Junior Achievement of Greater Columbia, St. Joseph's Indian School, Mennonite Housing Rehabilitation Services, Big Brothers of Sedgwick County, Opera Guild of Greater Miami, Women in Distress of Broward County, Pennsylvania Ballet Association, Miami Rescue Mission, Cities in Schools of Palm Beach County, Black Heritage Museum, The Continuum/The Discovery Center, Habitat for Humanity of Greater Miami, New World Symphony, Stanford University Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University, Peoples Light and Theatre Company, The Greening of Detroit, Center for Creative Studies, Lyric Chamber Ensemble, Boy Scouts of America Chattahoochee Council, The Columbus Museum, Tallahassee Urban League, Saint Bernard's Church, Red River Valley Habitat for Humanity, Hospice at Charlotte, Long Beach Day Nursery, Sarah House, Long Beach Symphony Association, Baldwin County Board of Education, Horry Cultural Arts Council, Gulf Coast Community Foundation, YMCA of Akron, Central South Carolina Habitat for Humanity, Boulder Public Library Foundation, Community Food Share, Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, City of Boulder, American Federation of Arts, Sumter Historic Preservation Society, Center to Prevent Handgun Violence, International Press Institute, Mount Union College, Boys and Girls Clubs of Summit County, Akron Community Foundation, Crisis Assistance Ministry, Habitat for Humanity of Charlotte. Writeups for negative responses to proposals are also included.
      - Board Book, 1991 March (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
        Writeups of approved grants for: Festival of Nations, People's Emergency Center Community Playground, Drueding Infirmary-U.S. Catholic Conference, Philharmonic Orchestra of Florida, Cooperative Business Assistance Corporation, Dade Women's Welfare Coalition, Central State Hospital, Miami Bridge, Prichard Committee for Academic Excellence, YWCA of Lexington Kentucky, City of Aberdeen-Alexander Mitchell Library, Macon Symphony Orchestra, Good Neighbors, Tri-County Independent Living Center, Goodwill Industries of Michiana, Reef Relief, National Association of Black Journalists, American Press Institute, Carolina Children's Home, New Detroit, Boy Scouts of America Santa Clara County Council Inc., Gary Educational Development Foundation, United Way of Dade County, The Saint Paul Foundation, Portage Area Senior Services, Harmonie Park Playhouse, Junior Achievement of Santa Clara County, Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center, Community Hall Foundation, Haleakala Inc., Memorial Medical Center Foundation, Columbia Art Association, Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, Infants in Need, Crisis Assistance Ministry, Florence Fuller Child Development Center, St. Elizabeth's Day Home, United Hospital Foundation, YMCA of Greater Miami, Institute for the Community as Extended Family, Damiano of Duluth, Manatee County Girls Club, Long Beach Unified School District, Florida West Coast Symphony, Macon Junior College Foundation, Philadelphia Festival Theatre for New Plays, Grand People Incorporated, Starkey Development Center for Retarded, Clinica Campesina/Rural Health Clinic, Resources for Human Development, John Bartram Association, National Adoption Center, Spoleto Festival U.S.A., Center for Haitian Studies, Fort Wayne Jewish Federation, Arts Midwest, Creek Indian Heritage Memorial Association, The Elizabeth Blackwell Health Center for Women, Wolf Trap Foundation for the Performing Arts, The Bottom Line-Childcare Solutions, California State University Long Beach Foundation, Sarasota Ballet Series, Arlington Housing Options Plus Elderly Services, Michigan Dyslexia Institute, Actors Guild of Lexington, South Florida Jail Ministries, Philadelphia Maritime Museum, Philadelphia Dance Company, Please Touch Museum, Acme Acting Corporation, Daily Bread Food Bank, New World School of the Arts, Conservation Corps of Long Beach, Edwin Shaw Hospital Development Foundation, Greater Akron Musical Association, International House of Metrolina, Colorado Dance Festival, Teach for America. Writeups of negative responses to proposals are also included.
      - Board Book, 1991 June 20 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
        Writeups of approved grants for: Lake Superior Center, Manatee Players, YMCA of Metropolitan Detroit, Oakland University Department of Rhetoric and Communications, Boys Club of Baldwin County, The Poverello Center, Cleveland Play House, La Salle University, Lindsey Wilson College, Mariners Inn, 1000 Friends of Florida, Creative Arts Collective, Big Bend Hospice, The Washington Journalism Center, White-Williams Foundation, Brandywine Graphic Workshop, Flint Hills Girl Scout Council, St. Paul Chamber Orchestra Society, The College Assistance Program of Dade County, Millan Theatre Company, Oakland Family Services, University of South Carolina Educational Foundation, Marygrove College, Dade Foundation, Community Services Agency, Raymond F. Kravis Center for the Performing Arts, Delphi Foundation Institute, Interval Brotherhood Homes Corporation, Georgia College Foundation, Fredric R. Mann Music Center, Columbia Free Medical Clinic, Seacamp Association, Musical Arts Association, Leadership Long Beach, Gulfport School District, United Cambodian Community, The Villages of Indiana, The Land Trust of Dade County, Columbus Philharmonic Guild, National Gallery of Art, Afro Carib American Cultural Center, Catholic Charities of San Jose, Community Accountants, Capital City Art Gallery Association, Drexel University, Friends of WLRN, Columbus 500, Concert Association of Greater Miami, Murray Dranoff Foundation, Seagull Industries for the Disabled, Aids Help Inc., New Freedom Theatre, The Philadelphia Orchestra Association, Epworth Village West, Community Womens Education Project, John W. Coltrane Cultural Society, Wooster Interfaith Housing Corporation, The House of Ichthus, Florida International University Foundation, Boys Hope, Area Performance Gallery, Akron Blind Center and Workshop, Eastern Kentucky University Foundation, Lees College, Ohio Chamber Ballet, The U.S. Baltic Foundation, Michigan Friends of Education, The Institute for Journalism Education, Community Services of Oakland, Dance Theatre of Harlem, American Council for the Arts, Metropolitan Opera Association, First Amendment Congress, B. Johnson Ministries, Cupertino Community Services, South Santa Clara County Housing Development Corporation, United Way of Manatee County, Twin Cities Public Television, Public Library of Charlotte and Mecklenburg County, Music Theatre of Wichita, Wichita Children's Home, Tallahassee Symphony Orchestra Inc., Anthony Wayne Rehabilitation Center for Handicapped, American Rivers Inc., American Indian College Fund, National Hispana Leadership Institute, Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank, School of Journalism Foundation of North Carolina, Fort Wayne PTA Association Council, University of Akron Foundation, Dade Foundation, Miami Museum of Science and Space Transit Planetarium. Writeups of negative responses to proposals are also included.
      - Board Book, 1991 September 19 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)